<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kalgebramobile</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">جبرك للمحمول</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">KAlgebra - мобилна версия</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KAlgebra mòbil</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KAlgebra mòbil</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Mobilní KAlgebra</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KAlgebra mugikorra</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KAlgebra לניידים</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">მობილური KAlgebra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KAlgebra 모바일</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KAlgebra-mobiel</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KAlgebra mobil</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਕੇ-ਐਲਜਬਰਾ ਮੋਬਾਇਲ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Przenośna KAlgebra</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KAlgebra Móvel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KAlgebra Móvel</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Мобильная KAlgebra</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Mobil Kalgebra</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Cebir Cep</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Мобільна KAlgebra</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKAlgebra Mobilexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KAlgebra 移动版</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KAlgebra 行動版</name>
  <summary>Graph Calculator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">حاسبة رسومية</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Графичен калкулатор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Calculadora gràfica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Calculadora gràfica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Kalkulačka grafů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Graphenrechner</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Υπολογιστής γραφημάτων</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Graph Calculator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Grafea Kalkulilo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Calculadora gráfica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Graafide arvutaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Kalkulagailu grafikoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kaaviolaskin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Calculatrice graphique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Calculadora gráfica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מחשבון תרשימים</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Számológép</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Calculator Graphic</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Kalkulator Grafik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Calcolatrice grafica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">გრაფიკული კალკულატორი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">그래핑 계산기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Rekenmachine met grafieken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Grafkalkulator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਗਰਾਫ਼ ਕੈਲਕੂਲਟਰ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Kalkulator wykresów</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Calculadora de Grafos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Calculadora gráfica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Графический калькулятор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Grafická kalkulačka</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Kalkulator grafov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Grafräknare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Grafik Hesap Makinesi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Графічний калькулятор</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxGraph Calculatorxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">图形计算器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">圖形計算機</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KAlgebra is an application that can replace your graphing calculator. It has numerical, logical, symbolic, and analysis features that let you calculate mathematical expressions on the console and graphically plot the results in 2D or 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">هو أحد التطبيقات التي يمكن أن تحل محل آلة حاسبة الرسوم البيانية الخاصة بك. يحتوي على ميزات عددية ومنطقية ورمزية وتحليلية تتيح لك حساب التعبيرات الرياضية على وحدة التحكم ورسم النتائج بيانياً ثنائي الأبعاد أو ثلاثي الأبعاد.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">KAlgebra е приложение, което може да замени вашия графичен калкулатор. То разполага с числени, логически, символни и аналитични функции, които ви позволяват да изчислявате математически изрази на конзолата и да изобразявате графично резултатите в 2D или 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KAlgebra és una aplicació que pot substituir la calculadora gràfica. Té característiques numèriques, lògiques, simbòliques, i analítiques que permeten calcular expressions matemàtiques a la consola i dibuixar gràficament els resultats en 2D o 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KAlgebra és una aplicació que pot substituir la calculadora gràfica. Té característiques numèriques, lògiques, simbòliques, i analítiques que permeten calcular expressions matemàtiques en la consola i dibuixar gràficament els resultats en 2D o 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KAlgebra ist eine Anwendung, die Ihren grafischen Taschenrechner ersetzt. Es  hat numerische, logische, symbolische und analytische Fähigkeiten, mit denen Sie mathematische Ausdrücke im Rechner auswerten und die Ergebnisse zwei- oder dreidimensional darstellen können.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Η KAlgebra είναι μία εφαρμογή αντικατάστασης του υπολογιστή για τα γραφικά σας. Έχει αριθμητικές, λογικές, συμβολικές και αναλυτικές λειτουργίες για να υπολογίζετε μαθηματικές εκφράσεις στην κονσόλα και να αναπαριστάτε γραφικά τα αποτελέσματα σε 2 ή 3 διαστάσεις.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KAlgebra is an application that can replace your graphing calculator. It has numerical, logical, symbolic, and analysis features that let you calculate mathematical expressions on the console and graphically plot the results in 2D or 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KAlgebra estas aplikaĵo, kiu povas anstataŭigi vian grafikan kalkulilon. Ĝi havas nombrajn, logikajn, simbolajn kaj analizajn funkciojn, kiuj ebligas al vi kalkuli matematikajn esprimojn sur la konzolo kaj grafike kalkuli la rezultojn en 2D aŭ 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KAlgebra es una aplicación que puede sustituir a su calculadora gráfica. Posee funciones numéricas, lógicas, simbólicas y de análisis que le permiten calcular expresiones matemáticas en la consola y representar gráficamente el resultado en 2 o 3 dimensiones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KAlgebra on rakendus, mis võib asendada su senist graafikalkulaatorit Sel on arvulisi, loogilisi, sümbolilisi ja analüüsiomadusi, mis võimaldavad arvutada matemaatilisi avaldisi konsoolis ja lasta tulemusi kujutada graafiliselt nii tasapinnaliselt (2D) kui ka ruumiliselt (3D).</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KAlgebra zure kalkulagailu grafikoa ordezka dezakeen aplikazio bat da. Kontsolan adierazpen matematikoak kalkulatzen eta emaitzak 2D edo 3Dtan grafikoki trazatzen uzten dizuten ezaugarriak ditu, zenbakizkoak, logikoak, sinbolikoak, eta analisikoak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KAlgebra on sovellus, joka voi korvata kaaviolaskimesi. Siinä on numeeriset, loogiset, symboliset ja analyysiominaisuudet, joiden avulla voit laskea matemaattisia lausekkeita konsolissa ja graafisesti kuvata tulokset kaksi- tai kolmiulotteisena.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KAlgebra est une application qui peut remplacer votre calculatrice graphique. Elle fournit des fonctions pour le calcul numérique, logique, symbolique et l'analyse qui vous permettent de calculer des expressions mathématiques dans la console et tracer graphiquement les résultats en 2D ou 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KAlgebra é unha aplicación que pode substituír as calculadoras gráficas. Ten funcionalidades numéricas, lóxicas, simbólicas e de análise que permiten calcular expresións matemáticas na consola e trazar graficamente os resultados en 2D ou 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KAlgebra הוא יישום שיכול להחליף את מחשבון התרשימים שלך. יש לו יכולות מספריות, לוגיות, סמליות וניתוח שיאפשרו לך לחשב ביטויים מתמטיים במסוף ולשרטט את התוצאות בצורה גרפית בדו־ממד או תלת־ממד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KAlgebra egy olyan alkalmazás, amely helyettesítheti a grafikus számológépet. Numerikus, logikai, szimbolikus és analízis funkciókkal rendelkezik, amelyek segítségével matematikai kifejezéseket számolhat a konzolon, és az eredményeket grafikusan ábrázolhatja 2D-ben vagy 3D-ben.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KAlgebra es un application que pote reimplaciare tu calculator graphic. Il ha characteristicas numeric, logic, symbolic, e de analysis que te permitte calcular expressiones mathematic expressions sur le consolle e traciar  graphicamente le resultatos in 2D o 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KAlgebra adalah aplikasi yang dapat menggantikan kalkulator grafikmu. Ini memiliki fitur numerik, logis, simbolis, dan analisis yang memungkinkanmu menghitung ekspresi matematis pada konsol dan secara grafik memplot hasilnya dalam 2D atau 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KAlgebra è un'applicazione che può sostituire la tua calcolatrice grafica. Ha funzionalità numeriche, logiche, simboliche e di analisi che ti permettono di calcolare le espressioni matematiche sulla console e di visualizzarne il grafico in 2D o 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KAlgebra აპლიკაციაა, რომელსაც თქვენი კალკულატორის ჩანაცვლება შეუძლია. მას გააჩნია რიცხვითი, ლოგიკური, სიმბოლური და ანალიზის თვისებები, რომლებიც საშუალებას გაძლევთ, მათემატიკური გამოსახულებები კონსოლში გამოთვალოთ და მათი გრაფიკები 2 ან 3 განზომილებიან სივრცეში დახატოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KAlgebra는 그래핑 계산기를 대체할 수 있는 앱입니다. 수학, 논리, 기호, 분석 기능이 있으며 콘솔에서 수식을 계산하고 2D나 3D로 결과를 플롯할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KAlgebra is een toepassing die uw grafische rekenmachine kan vervangen. Het heeft numerieke, logische, symbolische en analyse functies die u mathematische expressies op de console laar berekenen en de resultaten grafisch plot in 2D of 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KAlgebra er eit program du kan bruka som ein grafkalkulator. Programmet støttar tal, logiske operatorar, symbol og analyse­funksjonar som lèt deg rekna ut matematiske uttrykk og visa dei grafisk, både i 2D og 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KAlgebra jest programem, który może zastąpić twój kalkulator graficzny. Ma możliwość przeprowadzania analiz numerycznych, logicznych i  symbolicznych, które umożliwiają obliczanie wyrażeń matematycznych w konsoli i rysowanie wyników w 2D lub 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KAlgebra é uma aplicação que poderá substituir a sua calculadora gráfica. Tem funcionalidades numéricas, lógicas, simbólicas e analíticas que lhe permitem calcular expressões matemáticas na consola e lhe permite desenhar de forma gráfica os resultados em 2D e 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KAlgebra é um aplicativo que poderá substituir a sua calculadora gráfica. Tem funcionalidades numéricas, lógicas, simbólicas e analíticas que lhe permitem calcular expressões matemáticas no console e também desenhar de forma gráfica os resultados em 2D e 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KAlgebra — программа-калькулятор с функцией построения графиков. Позволяет вычислять значения выражений и строить двумерные и трёхмерные графики функций.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KAlgebra je aplikácia, ktorá vie nahradiť vašu grafickú kalkulačku. Má numerické, logické, symbolické a analytické funkcie, ktoré vám umožnia vypočítať matematické výrazy na konzole a graficky znázorniť výsledky v 2D alebo 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KAlgebra je aplikacija, ki lahko nadomesti vaš grafični kalkulator. Ima numerične, logične, simbolične in analizne funkcije, ki omogočajo izračunavanje matematičnih izrazov na konzoli in rezultate narišejo v 2D ali 3D grafu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kalgebra är en applikation som kan ersätta en grafräknare. Den har numeriska, logiska, symboliska och analytiska funktioner som låter dig beräkna matematiska uttryck i terminalen och rita upp resultaten grafiskt med två eller tre dimensioner.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Cebir, grafik hesap makinenızın yerine geçebilecek bir uygulamadır. Sayısal, mantıksal, sembolik ve analiz özellikleriyle, uçbirim üzerinden matematiksel ifadeleri hesaplayabilir ve sonuçları 2B veya 3B olarak olarak grafik olarak çizdirebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KAlgebra — програма, яка може замінити вам графічний калькулятор. У ній ви знайдете можливості з числового, логічного, символічного аналізу, які нададуть вам змогу обчислювати математичні вирази у консолі і графічно будувати результати на площині або у просторі.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKAlgebra is an application that can replace your graphing calculator. It has numerical, logical, symbolic, and analysis features that let you calculate mathematical expressions on the console and graphically plot the results in 2D or 3D.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KAlgebra可以代替您的其他图形计算器。它包含数值计算、逻辑计算、符号计算，以及分析功能，能让您在控制台中计算数学表达式，并将函数结果绘制为2D或3D图像。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KAlgebra 是個能替代繪圖計算機的應用程式，它包含數字、邏輯、符號以及分析功能，讓您能在終端計算數學表達式，並用圖形化的方式以 2D 或 3D 繪製結果。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kalgebra</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kalgebra</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kalgebra</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kalgebra&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalgebra/kalgebra.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalgebra/kalgebra-plot2d.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kalgebra/kalgebra-mobile.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kalgebramobile.desktop</launchable>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kalgebramobile</binary>
  </provides>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::google_play">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.kde.kalgebramobile</value>
  </custom>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
