<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kalgebra.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KAlgebra mòbil</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KAlgebra-mobiel</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KAlgebra Móvel</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KAlgebra Mobile</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKAlgebra Mobilexx</name>
  <summary>Graph Calculator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Calculadora gràfica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Calculatrice graphique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Rekenmachine met grafieken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Calculadora de Grafos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Grafická kalkulačka</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxGraph Calculatorxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KAlgebra is an application that can replace your graphing calculator. It has numerical, logical, symbolic, and analysis features that let you calculate mathematical expressions on the console and graphically plot the results in 2D or 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KAlgebra és una aplicació que pot substituir la calculadora gràfica. Té característiques numèriques, lògiques, simbòliques, i analítiques que permeten calcular expressions matemàtiques a la consola i dibuixar gràficament els resultats en 2D o 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KAlgebra est une application qui peut remplacer votre calculatrice graphique. Elle fournit des fonctions pour le calcul numérique, logique, symbolique et l'analyse qui vous permettent de calculer des expressions mathématiques dans la console et tracer graphiquement les résultats en 2D ou 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KAlgebra is een toepassing die uw grafische rekenmachine kan vervangen. Het heeft numerieke, logische, symbolische en analyse functies die u mathematische expressies op de console laar berekenen en de resultaten grafisch plot in 2D of 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KAlgebra é uma aplicação que poderá substituir a sua calculadora gráfica. Tem funcionalidades numéricas, lógicas, simbólicas e analíticas que lhe permitem calcular expressões matemáticas na consola e lhe permite desenhar de forma gráfica os resultados em 2D e 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KAlgebra je aplikácia, ktorá vie nahradiť vašu grafickú kalkulačku. Má numerické, logické, symbolické a analytické funkcie, ktoré vám umožnia vypočítať matematické výrazy na konzole a graficky znázorniť výsledky v 2D alebo 3D.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKAlgebra is an application that can replace your graphing calculator. It has numerical, logical, symbolic, and analysis features that let you calculate mathematical expressions on the console and graphically plot the results in 2D or 3D.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://edu.kde.org/kalgebra/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kalgebra</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdeedu/kalgebra/index.html</url>
  <url type="donation">https://kde.org/donate/</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kalgebra.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kalgebramobile</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
